<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RISK - probability calculator</string>

    <string name="help_overall1">Welcome to the Guide for the app \"RISK - probability
        calculator\"</string>
    <string name="help_overall2">For RISK-rules, please have a look at the rulebook, delivered with
        the game. </string>
    <string name="help_overall3">Important for this app is to know how a war works. In a war is a
        player attacking a field from another player. From the RISK rules, there is given, that an
        attacker can attack with at most three dices and a defender defend with at most two
        dices. After each throw of the dices, a dice-war ends. This is important, since now the
        probabilities that someone wins, is going to be updated.</string>

    <string name="help_field1">Enter your attacking units, as well as defending units which are
        located on the fields, which you\'re planning to attack.</string>
    <string name="help_field2">You must fill in at least your attacking units and the defending
        units for field number 1. If the entered number one a field  is bigger than 75, then the units
        on this field will be set to 75.</string>
    <string name="help_field3">After all troops are entered as wished, press Calculate</string>

    <string name="help_calculation1">For each defending field which was entered before, there is
        now a line shown with following values: </string>
    <string name="help_calculation2">Number of Attacker, Number of Defender, Number of expected
        remaining Attackers, Number of expected remaining Defenders, Probability that Attacker
        wins, Probability that Defender wins</string>
    <string name="help_calculation3">Caution: If the probability that one side wins is 100\% and the
        other 0%, means not that one can not loose. The probability for the 0\% part is just small
        enough that it has to be rounded to 0 and therefore the counter-probability is 100.</string>
    <string name="help_calculation4">Choose one line which you\'re going to attack. Press this line
        and the next screen will open</string>

    <string name="help_playAndPress1">On top are the same values as before in the list, but now
        only for the chosen field.</string>
    <string name="help_playAndPress2">Depending on current Attacker and Defender are multiple
        buttons shown.</string>
    <string name="help_playAndPress3">The two buttons on the left side, are pressed if the attacker
        lost one or two armies.</string>
    <string name="help_playAndPress4">The two buttons on the right side are pressed if the defender
        lost one or two armies.</string>
    <string name="help_playAndPress5">The button in the middle is pressed if both sides lost one
        army.</string>
    <string name="help_playAndPress6">After each button-press, the values above will be updated.
        Press a button each time, a dice-war has ended</string>


    <string name="input_field_1">Enter at least for field 1 numbers of Attacking and Defending Units</string>

    <string name="calculate_button">Calculate</string>
    <string name="input_field_defending_units_on_field_1">Defending Units on Field 1:</string>
    <string name="input_field_attacking_units_on_field">Attacking Units on Field  :</string>
    <string name="input_field_defending_units_on_field_2">Defending Units on Field 2:</string>
    <string name="input_field_defending_units_on_field_3">Defending Units on Field 3:</string>
    <string name="input_field_defending_units_on_field_4">Defending Units on Field 4:</string>
    <string name="input_field_defending_units_on_field_5">Defending Units on Field 5:</string>
    <string name="input_field_defending_units_on_field_6">Defending Units on Field 6:</string>
    <string name="attacker"># A</string>
    <string name="defender"># D</string>
    <string name="remaining_attacker">surv. A</string>
    <string name="remaining_defender">surv. D</string>
    <string name="attacker_win_with">Win A</string>
    <string name="both_minus_1">A-1 D-1</string>
    <string name="defender_win_with">Win D</string>
    <string name="attacker_side_min_2">A-2</string>
    <string name="attacker_side_min_1">A-1</string>
    <string name="defender_side_min_2">D-2</string>
    <string name="defender_side_min_1">D-1</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="chose_field_of_interest">Chose field of interest</string>

    <string name="main_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="main_help">Help</string>


</resources>